我不会惹祸吧 比尔?
Sure I won't get in trouble, Bill?
别这么胆 胆 胆小嘛
Don't be a wuss.
如果我没病入膏肓肯定跟你一起 起 起去
I'd come with you if I weren't dying.
你没病得那么重
You're not dying!
你没见我今早飞流鼻 鼻涕三千尺吗?
You didn't see the vomit coming out of my nose this morning?
真够恶心的
That's disgusting.
行啦 给我拿点石蜡过来
Okay. Go get the wax.
得去地窖拿吗?
In the cellar?
不是你说要玩纸船漂 漂流的吗?
You want it to float, don't you?
好吧
Fine.
乔治
Georgie.
快点哦
Hurry up.
我一点都不怕
Okay. I'm brave.
蜡放在哪了?
Where's the wax?
找到了
There's the wax.
就在这
Yes.
那是什么? 那是什么?
What was that? What's that?
天啊
Oh, jeez.
好啦
All right.
做好啦
There you go.
她可 可 可以出航了 船长
She's all ready, Captain.
她?
She?
船都得用"她"来称呼的
You always call boats "she".
她就她吧
"She".
谢谢你 比尔
Thanks, Billy.
待会儿见 拜拜
See you later. Bye.
注意安全
Be careful.
不
No!
比尔知道了会气炸了的
Oh, Bill's gonna kill me.
你好呀 乔治
Hiya, Georgie.
这船真漂亮…
What a nice boat.
你想拿回去吗?
Do you want it back?
是的 麻烦你还给我
Um, yes, please.
你像是个乖孩子 我猜你肯定有不少朋友吧
You look like a nice boy. I bet you have a lot of friends.
我有三个好朋友 不过我跟我哥哥是最最要好的
Three, but my brother's my best best.
他在哪?
Where is he?
他病了 一直卧床休息呢
In bed. Sick.
我想我能让他好起来 我会给他个气球做礼物
I bet I can cheer him up. I'll give him a balloon.
乔治 你也想要个气球吗?
Do you want a balloon too, Georgie?
妈妈告诉我不能收陌生人给的东西
I'm not supposed to take stuff from strangers.
好吧 我叫潘尼怀斯 是个会跳舞的小丑
Oh... Well, I'm Pennywise the Dancing Clown.
潘尼怀斯在这见过乔治
Pennywise? Yes. Meet Georgie.
乔治也算是见过潘尼怀斯啦
Georgie, meet Pennywise.
现在我们就不算是陌生了 是吧?
Now we aren't strangers, are we?
你怎么跑到下水道里了?
What are you doing in the sewer?
是风暴把我丢进了这里
A storm blew me away.
整个马戏团都遭到了风暴袭击
Blew the whole circus away.
你能闻到马戏团独有的味道吗 乔治?
Can you smell the circus, Georgie?
有花生 棉花糖
There's peanuts, cotton candy,
热狗
hot dogs,
还有
and...
爆米花?
Popcorn?
对 爆米花 是你的最爱吗?
Popcorn! Is that your favorite?
- 对呀 - 也是我的最爱
- Uh-huh. - Mine, too.
因为爆米花会爆裂开 噗噗噗的
Because they pop. Pop, pop, pop.
噗 噗 噗
Pop, pop, pop.
噗
Pop.
我该回家了
I should get going now.
哦
Oh.
不要你的船了吗?
Without your boat?
你不会不要它的 是吧乔治
You don't wanna lose it, Georgie.
比尔可是会被你气炸的哦
Bill's gonna kill you.
给你
Here.
拿回去吧
Take it.
拿回去啊 乔治
Take it, Georgie.
救命啊
Help!
比尔
Billy!
《小丑回魂》
扣扳机啊 麦克
Pull it, Mike.
动手啊 扣扳机
Go on now, pull it.
给 去装弹
Here, reload it.
麦克 你必须开始承担更多的责任了
You need to start taking more responsibility around here, Mike.
你父亲比你现在这个年纪还小的时候就…
Your dad was younger than you when he took...
我不是我爸爸 好吗?
I'm not my dad, okay?
是啊
Yeah.
小子 看着我
Look at me, son.
我说看着我
Look at me!
这世界你只能做两种人
There are two places you can be in this world.
一种是跟我们一样做个拿枪的人 另一种就是
You can be out here like us or you can be in there,
挨枪子的畜生
like them.
如果你再磨磨蹭蹭地犹豫不决
You waste time hemming and hawing,
迟早有一天你的命运将由他人掌控
and someone else is gonna make that choice for you.
而你在死之前都不会知道是被谁玩弄于鼓掌之中
Except you won't know it until you feel that bolt between your eyes.
有个犹太人教堂 你知道吧?
So, there's this church full of Jews, right?
斯坦利必须在那完成他的超级犹太式成人礼
And Stan has to take this super Jewy test.
怎么完成?
But how's it work?
他们会把他小丁丁的尖儿切掉
They slice the tip of his dick off.
但要是这样的话 斯坦利就成太监了啊
But then Stan will have nothing left!
- 你说的对 - 等等我 伙计们
- That's true. - Wait up, you guys!
嘿 斯坦利 你的成人礼到底是个什么流程?
Hey, Stan, what happens at the Bar Mitzvah, anyways?
埃迪说他们会给你小丁丁的尖儿切 切 切掉
Ed says they slice the tip of your dick off.
对啊 我觉着是这样 犹太教祭祀会脱掉你的裤子
Yeah, and I think the rabbi's gonna pull down your pants,
然后面向所有人说 "你的小丁丁呢?"
turn to the crowd and say, "Where's the beef?"
在成人礼上 我会朗读《摩西五经》
At the Bar Mitzvah, I read from the Torah,
然后还要发表讲话 经历这些后我就变成男人了
and then I make a speech and suddenly, I become a man.
我能想到更嗨皮的方式过我的成人礼
I could think of funner ways to become a man.
"更嗨皮"指的是…
"More fun" you mean.
倒霉
Oh, shit.
你觉着他们会在我的纪念册上签名留言吗?
Think they'll sign my yearbook?
"亲爱的里奇
"Dear Richie,
上个月在你书包里拉了一坨还冒热乎气的翔 抱歉啦
sorry for taking a hot, steaming dump in your backpack last March.
祝你暑假愉快"
Have a good summer. "
你是独自藏在厕所间里吗 "海狸"利?
Are you in there by yourself, Beaver-ly?
还是说你正跟全校半数男生鬼混呢啊 浪货?
Or do you have half the guys in the school with you, huh, slut?
我知道你在里面 你个小贱人 我能闻到你身上骚味
I know you're in there, little shit. I can smell you.
你这骚样能有朋友就怪了
No wonder you don't have any friends.
到底是哪个词 格里塔 浪货还是小贱人?
Which is it, Gretta? Am I a slut or a little shit?
想好再喷吧
Make up your mind.
你就是个垃圾
You're trash.
我们只不过是想给你提个醒
We just wanted to remind you.
真是个废物
Such a loser.
至少你现在骚味不那么重了
Well, at least now you'll smell better.
真恶心
Gross.
咱们走
Let's go, girls.
祝你暑假愉快 "海狸"利
Have a nice summer, Beaver-ly.
真可悲
Pathetic.
感觉爽爆了
Best feeling ever.
这就爽了?
Yeah?
你试试吧 撸管比这爽得多
Try tickling your pickle for the first time.
你们明天有什么计划吗?
Hey, what do you guys wanna do tomorrow?
我要开始训练了
I start my training.
- 训练什么? - 街头霸王啊
- Wait, what training? - Street Fighter.
你准备把一整个暑假都用在玩街机上?
Is that how you wanna spend your summer? Inside of an arcade?
总比你整天窝在你妈妈身边要强
Beats spending it inside of your mother.
- 哦 - 那我们去矿场怎么样?
- Oh! - What if we go to the quarry?
兄弟们 我们还得去荒 荒地呢
Guys, we have the Barrens.
对
Right.
贝蒂·瑞普森的妈妈
Betty Ripsom's mom.
她还指望能在学校接到孩子吗?
Is she really expecting to see her come out of that school?
我不知道
I don't know.
似乎贝蒂这几周一直在躲着大家
As if Betty Ripsom's been hiding in Home Ec. for the last few weeks.
你觉着警察会找到她吗?
You think they'll actually find her?
肯定能
Sure.
他们会在阴沟里找到已腐烂的贝蒂 浑身爬满蛆虫
In a ditch. All decomposed, covered in worms and maggots.
闻着就像埃迪他妈妈的内裤
Smelling like Eddie's mom's underwear.
闭嘴吧你 真恶心
Shut up! That's freaking disgusting.
她没死 她只是失 失 失踪了
She's not dead. She's missing.
抱歉比尔 她只是失踪了
Sorry, Bill. She's missing.
其实荒地那也不是很糟糕啦
You know the Barrens aren't that bad.
没谁会不喜欢在臭水沟里嬉戏吧?
Who doesn't love splashing around in shitty water?
这飞盘挺好啊 你个死玻璃
Nice Frisbee, flamer.
还给我
Give it back!
一帮废物
Fucking losers!
废物
Loser.
你才是废 废 废物 鲍尔斯
You suck, Bowers.
快别这么说 比尔
Shut up, Bill.
你刚才说 说 说什么 比 比 比尔?
You say something, Billy?
我们给你免虐卡是因为你弟弟死了
You got a free ride this year 'cause of your little brother.
现在卡到期了 登布洛
Ride's over, Denbrough.
这个暑假老子要玩死你们这帮废物
This summer's gonna be a hurt train for you and your faggot friends.
我希望失踪的那个是他
I wish he'd go missing.
可能就是他把贝蒂绑了
He's probably the one doing it.
你是打算让我过去呢
You gonna let me go by?
还是说得有什么口令才行?
Or is there a secret password or something?
哦
Oh.
- 抱歉 - 抱歉可算不上是
- Um, sorry. - Sorry isn't...
口令
A password.
亨利那伙人渣在学校西门那边呢
Henry and his goons are over by the west entrance.
所以你应该不会有麻烦
So you should be fine.
我不是
Oh, I wasn't...
大家都知道他们在堵你
Everyone knows he's looking for you.
你听谁的歌呢?
What you listening to?
新街边男孩
New Kids on the Block.
我压根就不喜欢这乐队 我只是…
I don't even like them. I was just...
等等 他们都叫你新来的 对吧? 那我就懂了
Wait. You're the new kid, right? Now I get it.
没什么可懂的
There's nothing to get.
我跟你闹着玩呢
I'm just messing with you.
我叫贝弗利·马什
I'm Beverly Marsh.
我认识你的 我们一起上过课的
Yeah. I know that 'cause we're in the same class.
社会课 你叫…
Social Studies. And you were...
我叫本 不过大家都叫我…
I'm Ben. But pretty much everybody just calls me...
新来的
The new kid.
没事 本 这在绰号界算是好的了
Well, Ben, there are worse things to be called.
我给你签纪念册吧
Let me sign this.
慢慢适应这吧 社会课的本同学
Stay cool, Ben from sosh class.
啊 我会的
Uh, yeah.
你也是 贝弗利
You too, Beverly.
撑住 新街边男孩
Hang tough, new kid on the block.
"妹子别走"
"Please Don't Go, Girl. "
这是新街边男孩的另一首歌
That's the name of another New Kids on the Block song.
绕口令:只见他猛挥拳头往柱子上砸
"He thrusts his fists against the posts...
只见他猛挥拳头往 往…
"He thrusts his fists against...
操
Shit!
柱子上砸
"Post. "
用帮忙吗? 我…
Need some help? I...
之前我们不是说好了的么?
I thought we agreed.
- 你先别急着说我… - 比尔
- Before you say anything... - Bill.
先看看我的想法
Just let me show you something first.
荒地
The Barrens.
在那我们一定能找到乔治
It's the only place that Georgie could have ended up.
他死了 比尔
He's gone, Bill.
但若真是风暴给他刮跑了 我们应该去…
But if the storm swept Georgie in, we should have gone...
他死了 死了
He's gone! He's dead!
他死了 我们什么也做不了
He's dead! There is nothing we can do! Nothing!
赶紧把那堆玩意拆了 别让你妈妈看到
Now take this down before your mother sees it.
如果你下次想从我办公室拿什么东西的话
Next time you wanna take something from my office...
必须经我允许
Ask.
你的管道又归你了
I guess you get your tunnels back.
上车啊 小妞
Get in!
变态
Creep!
天啊
Oh, Jesus.
麦克
Mike!
快点 儿子
Hurry, son!
救我 烧过来了
Help! It burns!
麦克
Mike!
别他妈让我再看到你
Stay the fuck outta my town!
麦克?
Mike?
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
你怎么就学不会呢 斯坦利
You're not studying, Stanley.
大家会怎么看我?
How's it going to look?
犹太教祭祀的亲儿子居然读不完《摩西五经》
The rabbi's son can't finish his own Torah reading.
把书放回到我办公室
Take the book to my office.
你根本没用心学
Obviously you're not using it.
除了特价小吃什么都可以拿
Take everything but the Delicious Deals, guys.
我妈妈喜欢吃那些小吃
My mom loves them.
嘿 起初你说去荒地 现在你又说去下水道里
Hey! First you said the Barrens, and now you're saying the sewer.
如果我们被抓了怎么办?
I mean, what if we get caught?
不会的 埃迪 下水道属于为百姓而建的市政工程
We won't, Eds. The sewers are public works.
我们不也是老百姓嘛 对吧?
We're the public, aren't we?
埃迪 这些是避孕药吗?
Hey, Eddie, these your birth control pills?
对 给你妹用的 这是私人物品
Yeah, and I'm saving it for your sister. This is private stuff.
我的小埃迪熊 你和朋友们赶着去哪啊?
Eddie Bear, where you boys off to in such a rush?
呃
Um...
去我 我 我家后院 卡斯布拉克夫人
Just my backyard, Mrs. K.
我买了新的…
I got a new...
- 新槌球套装 - 天啊 你就不能说话利索点儿吗
- A new croquet set. - Jeez, spit it out, Bill!
准了
Okay.
宝贝儿 千万别在草上打滚哈
Oh, and sweetie, don't go rolling around on the grass.
尤其是刚割过的草
Especially if it's just been cut.
要是过敏症犯了可有你受的
You know how bad your allergies can get.
遵命 母上 我们出发吧
Yes, Mom. Let's go.
你是不是忘了什么?
Aren't you forgetting something?
卡斯布拉克女士 要不要我也亲你一口呀?
Do you want one from me too, Mrs. K?
- 我就是开个玩笑 - 不不不
- I was kidding. - No, no, no.
抱歉 母上
Sorry, Mommy.
"君之红发婉如冬日烈火 而燃至柳月的余烬
"Your hair is winter fire, January embers...
亦为我心焚炼之地"
My heart burns there too. "
骑慢点
Slow down!
银神驹 冲啊
Hi-ho, Silver!
冲啊
Away!
你那老自行车居然比们的还快
Your old lady bike's too fast for us!
书给你找到了
Found it.
你们现在不是放暑假呢吗?
Isn't it summer vacation?
我觉着你应该出去玩玩 别整天泡在书堆里
I would think you'd be ready to take a break from the books.
我喜欢在这读书
I like it in here.
男孩儿嘛 暑假就应该找朋友们一起出去玩耍
A boy should be spending his summer outside with friends.
你没有朋友吗?
Don't you have any friends?
能把书给我了吗?
Can I have the book now?
拿蛋的小胖子
Egg boy.
你在这干什么呢?
What on earth are you doing?
你去哪啊 大胸仔?
Where are you off to, tits?
往哪儿跑
Gotcha.
住手
Wait.
- 按住他 - 放开我
- Fucking hold him. - Leave me alone!
- 揍他 - 你别想跑
- Smack him. - Don't let tubby get away.
救命
Help!
按住他
Get him!
- 按住他 霍克斯德特 - 贝尔奇 抓好他
- Hold him, Hockstetter. - Get him, Belch.
住手
Stop!
- 放开我 - 看你这一身肥肉
- Just leave me alone. - Look at all this blubber!
看我把你发型烫成迈克尔·杰克逊同款
Let me light his hair, like Michael Jackson.
按住他
Just hold him.
放开我 快放开
Get off me! Get off me!
救命啊
Help!
听好了 新来的
Okay, new kid.
这座桥叫吻桥是有说法的
This is what us locals call the Kissing Bridge.
在这你得干两件事 一是亲亲脸蛋
It's famous for two things. Sucking face,
二是刻下名字
and carving names.
亨利 求求你
Henry, please.
够了 亨利
Whoa, whoa! Henry!
给我闭嘴
Shut up!
我要在他的奶酪肚子上刻上我的全名
I'm gonna carve my whole name onto this cottage cheese!
我他妈要砍掉你的奶子 我对天发誓
I'm gonna cut your fucking tits off. I swear to God!
去抓他
Get him!
快
Come on!
抓住他
Get him!
你跑不掉的
You can't run!
- 不好 - 我们得找到那头肥猪
- Oh, no! - We need to find Fatty!
我的刀呢 我老爹会揍死我的
My knife. My old man will kill me!
- 你们俩去抓他 - 我们走
- You two, get him! - Come on!
快他妈帮我找啊
Move your fucking ass!
他往那边跑了
He's going that way! Come on!
他在下面
He's down there.
我不知道 可能是吧
I don't know. I guess.
那是毒藤 那个也是
That's poison ivy. And that's poison ivy.
那个也是毒藤
And that's poison ivy.
哪个是? 毒藤在哪?
Where? Where's the poison ivy?
哪个也不是 不是他妈所有植物都是毒藤好吧 斯坦利?
Nowhere. Not every fucking plant is poison ivy, Stanley.
我现在身上发痒了
Okay, I'm starting to get itchy now...
对我来说这绝对不是个好征兆
and I'm pretty sure this is not good for my...
你跟你妈共享一个卫生间吗?
Do you use the same bathroom as your mother?
有时候会的
Sometimes, yeah.
那你可能身上有虱子了
Then you probably have crabs.
这一点也不好笑
That's so not funny.
你俩不进来吗?
Aren't you guys coming in?
我不进去 那可是灰水
Uh-uh. It's greywater.
灰水是他妈什么玩意?
What the hell's greywater?
就是尿和屎的混合液 我告诉你们
It's basically piss and shit. So I'm just telling you,
你们现在正游走于数百万加仑的德里人排泄物中
you guys are splashing around in millions of gallons of Derry pee. So...
你还真去闻啊? 你在干…
Are you serious? What are you...
这闻起来可不像屎啊 先生
Doesn't smell like caca to me, se?or.
拉倒吧 我在这都能闻得到
Okay, I can smell that from here.
可能只是你闻到你自己的口臭了
It's probably just your breath wafting back into your face.
你们没听过葡萄球菌感染吗?
Have you ever heard of a staph infection?
我把葡萄球菌拿给你看看怎么样
Oh, I'll show you a staff infection.
这太不卫生了
This is so unsanitary. You're literally...
你们现在就像是在马桶里游泳一样
This is literally like swimming inside of a toilet bowl right now.
你们没听过李斯特菌吗?
Have you ever heard of Listeria?
你是不是智障啊?
Are you retarded?
因为你 我们才来的这儿
You're the reason why we're in this position right now.
别吵了
Guys!
该死 别告诉我这个是…
Shit. Don't tell me that's...
不是
No.
乔治穿的是雨靴
Georgie wore galoshes.
那这是谁的鞋?
Whose sneaker is it?
是贝蒂·瑞普森的
It's Betty Ripsom's.
我操了
Oh, shit.
我的天啊 该死
Oh, God. Oh, fuck!
我不喜欢这个答案
I don't like this.
你们觉着贝蒂当时是什么感觉
How do you think Betty feels?
穿着一只鞋在地下水道里来回跑
Running around these tunnels with only one frickin' shoe?
她要是还在这管道里呢?
What if she's still here?
埃迪 进来啊
Eddie, come on!
我妈妈要是知道我们来这玩 她会气犯病了的
My mom will have an aneurysm, if she finds out that we're playing down here.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
比尔?
Bill?
如果我是贝蒂 我肯定希望有人来找我
If... If I was Betty Ripsom, I would want us to find me.
乔治也会这么想
Georgie too.
如果我不想找到他们呢?
What if I don't want to find them?
无意冒犯 比尔 只是我不想…
I mean, no offense, Bill, but I don't want to end up like...
我不想也变失踪了
I don't want to go missing either.
- 他说的也有道理 - 你也不来?
- He has a point. - You too?
现在是暑假
It's summer.
暑假就应该开心地玩耍
We're supposed to be having fun.
在这怎么开心
This isn't fun.
这又恐怖又恶心
This is scary and disgusting.
我了个擦 你怎么了?
Holy shit! What happened to you?
我听到你的声音了 大胸仔
I hear ya, tits.
别以为你能这在下面躲一整天
Don't think you can stay down here all damn day now.
你找到我们了 帕特里克
You found us, Patrick.
帕特里克
Patrick.
操
Fuck!
我认为我们救了新来的胖子是件好事
I think it's great that we're helping the new kid,
但是我们也得考虑自身的安全啊
but also we need to think of our own safety.
你看他血流的到处都是
I mean, he's bleeding all over and you guys know...
你们也知道现下艾滋病流行于世
that there's an AIDS epidemic happening right now as we speak, right?
我妈妈的一个朋友就得上了艾滋病
My mom's friend in New York City got it...
就因为碰了纽约地铁里的一个脏兮兮的电线杆
by touching a dirty pole on the subway.
感染艾滋病的血液是通过她手指上的倒刺进入她体内的
And a drop of AIDS blood got into his system through a hangnail. A hangnail!
手脚感染可以被截肢
And you can amputate legs and arms.
腰得怎么截?
But how do you amputate a waist?
你们肯定知道巷子里全是携带艾滋病毒的针头吧?
You guys do know that alleys are known for dirty needles that have AIDS, right?
你们肯定知道的吧
You guys do know that?
- 嘿… - 啊 我们完蛋了
- Hey... - Ah, we're screwed.
里奇 你在这守着 其他人跟我来
Richie, wait here. Come on.
能在你死之前认识你 我很荣幸
Glad I got to meet you before you died.
好了
Okay.
这些药品我们买得起吗?
Can we afford all that?
我们就这点儿钱
It's all we got.
你不是逗我呢吧?
You kidding me?
对了 我记得你能在这赊账吧?
Wait, you have an account here, don't you?
如果我妈妈知道我自己买了这么多药和医疗用品
If my mom finds out I bought all this stuff for myself...
本周余下的日子 我都会在急诊室的X光下度过
I'm spending the whole rest of the weekend in the emergency room getting X-rayed.
再见 爸爸
See you later, Dad.
再见 格里塔
See you, Gretta.
你还好吗?
You okay?
我好的很 你们在干嘛?
I'm fine. What's wrong with you?
跟你没关系
None of your business.
外面有个男孩被人屠的满身是血
There's a kid outside. Looked like someone killed him.
我们需要些医 医疗用品
We need some supplies,
但是我们钱不够
but we don't have enough money.
我很喜欢你眼镜 基恩先生
I like your glasses, Mr. Keene.
你戴上它就像是克拉克·肯特
You look just like Clark Kent.
哦
Oh.
从没人这么说过我
I don't know about that.
我能借你眼镜戴戴吗?
Can I try them?
当然可以
Mmm. Sure.
你觉得如何?
What do you think?
哇哦 这么说如何
Well, how about that?
你戴上眼镜就像是露易丝·莱恩
You look just like Lois Lane.
真的?
Really?
嗯
Mmm.
好啦 还给你
Well, here you go.
该死 我很抱歉
Shoot, I'm so sorry.
没关系
It's okay.
快吮吸伤口吧
Just suck the wound.
- 我得集中注意力 - 你还得集中注意力?
- I need to focus right now. - You need to focus?
对 你能帮我拿点东西过来吗?
Yeah, can you go get me something?
- 我的天啊 你需要什么? - 去拿我的近远视双用镜
- Jesus! What do you need? - Go get my bifocals.
在我第二个腰包里
I hid 'em in my second fanny pack.
你为什么有两个腰包?
Why do you have two fanny packs?
说来话长 不过我现在得专心救他
I need to focus right now and it's a long story.
反正我也不想听
I don't want to get into it.
那个 谢 谢 谢谢你了
Um, thanks.
我们扯平啦
Even-steven.
天啊 他在流血 天啊
Oh, God, he's bleeding. Oh, my God!
社会课的本同学?
Ben from sosh?
你必须先吮吸好伤口才能上绷带
You have to suck the wound before you apply the Band-Aids.
- 这是常识 - 你别在这不懂装懂了
- This is 101. - You don't know what you're talking about.
你还好吗? 伤看着挺重啊
Are you okay? That looks like it hurts.
我没事 就是刚才摔了一跤
Oh. No, I'm good. I just fell.
对 摔到亨利·鲍尔斯的刀上
Yeah, right into Henry Bowers.
别瞎说 里 里 里奇
Shut it, Richie.
为什么不说? 我又没胡诌
Why? It's the truth.
你确定他们治疗你的时候没乱用药品?
You sure they got the right stuff to fix you up?
我 我 我们会照顾好他的
You know, we'll take care of him.
再次感谢 贝弗利
Uh, thanks again, Beverly.
不客气 有缘再会
Sure. Maybe I'll see you around.
好啊 我们明天可能会想
Yeah, we were thinking about...
去矿 矿 矿场
going to the quarry tomorrow,
如果你也想…
if you wanna...
来的话
come.
我知道了 谢谢你的邀请
Good to know. Thanks.
干得漂亮 在她面前提及鲍尔斯
Nice going bringing up Bowers in front of her.
说的对 你不知道她们以前的事?
Yeah, dude, you heard what she did.
以前她干了什么?
What'd she do?
你该问她干了谁
More like "Who'd she do?"
我听说她上过的人的名单比我的丁丁都长
From what I hear, the list is longer than my wang.
那也没多少人
That's not saying much.
那只 只 只是谣言
They're just rumors.
总之呢 比尔三年级的时候就跟她扯上过
Anyway, Bill had her back in third grade.
他们在学校舞台剧上接吻了
They kissed in the school play.
评论上都说他俩接吻时的激情可不是演出来的
The reviews said you can't fake that sort of passion.
伙计们看 在这发现个胖子
Now, pip-pip and tally-ho, my good fellows,
我想这胖子需要我们全力帮助
I do believe this chap requires our utmost attention.
卡斯布拉克医生 赶紧去救他
Get in there, Dr. K. Come on, fix him up.
还用得着你这个卷毛脑袋废话 我知道我该干什么
Why don't you shut the fuck up, Einstein, because I know what I'm doing...
而且我很不喜欢你模仿英国人
and I don't want you doing the British guy with me right now.
赶紧吮吸伤口吧
Suck the wound. Get in there.
马桶和浴缸的废水
Toilet and bath water travel down...
从管道流入下水道
the drains and into the sewer.
跟你的伙伴们在下水道里玩会很有趣的
The sewer is a fun place to play with all of your friends.
跟着废水一起进入管道 然后看废水都流到哪去了
Just follow the water into the drains and down into the sewers you go.
你和伙伴们在下水道玩的时候 就像小丑一样傻的可爱
When you're with your friends in the sewers, you can be as silly as a clown!
说的对 这就是我们节目今天的主题
That's right, it's the word of the day.
嗨 老爸
Hi, Daddy.
嗨 小贝弗利
Hey, Bevvie.
你手里拿的什么?
Whatcha got there?
就是些小玩意
Just some things.
什么小玩意?
Like what?
告诉我 你还是我的小宝贝
Tell me you're still my little girl.
是的 老爸
Yes, Daddy.
那就好
Good.
左上的高弧掷球 这是他最后一次击球机会
A deep fly ball to the left. His last at bat.
球擦棒而过
He scratched the foul pole.
韦德·博格斯 毫无疑问他的击球冠绝联盟
Wade Boggs, of course, leads the league in hitting so far.
你喜欢这头发 我就全剪掉…
This is what you did. This is what you...
这是…
This is...
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
- 小菜一碟 - 可怜的小树
- So easy. - Poor tree.
超简单
So easy!
天啊 你痰吐的真烂 我赢了
Oh, my God, that was terrible. I win.
- 你赢了? - 当然
- You won? - Yeah.
- 你看到我吐的痰了么 - 我的痰飞得最远
- Did you see my loogie? - That went the farthest!
- 吐痰凭距离决胜负 - 是凭量 一直都是凭量决胜负
- It's by distance. - Mass. It's always been mass.
什么是量?
What is mass?
吐多远都无所谓
Who cares how far it goes?
关键是它看起来酷不酷 是绿的还是白的
It matters how cool it looks, like it's green or it's white...
唾沫是不是多 痰够不够浓
or juicy and fat.
- 好了 - 谢谢
- All right. - Thanks for that.
- 谁第一个跳 - 太可怕了
- Who's first? - That was terrible.
我来
I'll go!
一群胆小鬼
Sissies.
我勒个去
What the fuck!
操了 我们刚刚被一个女孩嘲笑了
Oh, holy shit! We just got showed up by a girl.
我们现在是不是必须得跳了?
Do we have to do that now?
是的
Yes.
跳啊
Come on!
该死
Oh, shit.
我赢了 我们已经赢了
I already won! We already won!
他们倒了 太棒了
They're down! Yes!
天 那是什么
Ah, fuck! What was that?
刚刚不知什么东西碰到了我的脚
Something just touched my foot right here.
怎么啦?
That work?
- 在哪? - 在这 在这
- Where are we looking? - Right here, right here!
一只乌龟而已
It's a turtle.
告诉你个新闻 本同学 现在学校已经放暑假了
News flash, Ben. School's out for summa!
哦 那 那可不是学校的东西
Oh, that? That's not school stuff.
- 这是谁送你的? - 没谁
- Who sent you this? - No one. Give it...
没谁
No one.
- 你收集这些旧报纸做什么? - 哦
- What's with the history project? - Oh...
我刚搬来这里的时候 没人跟我一起玩
When I first moved here, I didn't have anyone to hang out with,
所以我只好在图书馆里打发时间
so I just started spending time in the library.
你去了图书馆?
You went to the library?
那能有什么意思?
On purpose?
我想看看
Oh, I wanna see.
黑斑点是什么
What's The Black Spot?
黑斑点是一个夜总会
The Black Spot was a nightclub...
在十年前被狂热的种族主义者烧毁了
that was burned down years ago by that racist cult.
什么?
The what?
你不看热拉尔多的节目吗?
Don't you watch Geraldo?
你 你 你的头发
Your hair...
你的头发真漂亮 贝弗利
Your... Your hair is beautiful, Beverly.
哦
Oh.
谢谢
Right. Thanks.
来 给我看看
Here, pass it.
这怎么都是关于凶杀案和儿童失踪案的?
Why is it all murders and missing kids?
德里镇和我之前去过的任何一个镇都大不相同
Derry's not like any town I've ever been in before.
有人做过研究 研究显示
They did a study once, and it turns out...
这里人口失踪率和死亡率是全国平均水平的六倍
people die or disappear six times the national average.
你读过那篇研究?
You read that?
不只是大人
And that's just grown-ups.
孩子们处境更糟糕
Kids are worse.
非常 非常糟糕
Way, way worse.
如果你们还想看 我家里还有更多资料
I've got more stuff if you wanna see it.
不 不
No, no.
不要怕 告诉我们就行了
Don't freak out, just tell us.
好吧 我听说他有一辆过山车 一只宠物猩猩
Yeah. I heard he has a rollercoaster and a pet chimp...
和一个老人的骨头 是的
and an old guy's fucking bones. Yeah.
哇 哇 哇
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇哦
Wow.
我的房间很赞吧?
Cool, huh?
不 没什么可赞的
No. No, nothing cool.
真心没什么好的
There's nothing cool.
好吧 这很赞 等等 不 看错了
This is cool, right here. Wait, no. No, it's not cool.
那是什么?
What's that?
那个? 那是德里镇的建镇许可状
Oh, that? That's the charter for Derry Township.
发现书呆子一枚
Nerd alert.
其实它背后的故事还是挺有意思的
No, actually, it's really interesting.
起初德里镇就是一个诱捕海狸的地方
Derry started as a beaver trapping camp.
现在也是啊 我说的对吗 兄弟们?
Still is, am I right, boys?
91个人签署了《建镇许可状》后就有了现在的德里镇
Ninety-one people signed the charter that made Derry.
但于同年冬天 他们都消失得无影无踪
But later that winter, they all disappeared without a trace.
整个镇吗?
The entire camp?
有传闻说是印第安人干的
There were rumors of Indians,
但并未发现小镇有受到袭击的迹象
but no sign of an attack.
大家都认为定是遭遇了瘟疫或是什么别的原因
Everybody just thought it was a plague or something.
但感觉像
But it's like...
某一天 大家一觉醒来后就都走了
one day everybody just woke up and left.
唯一的线索是一些血衣 断断续续散在地上直至井房
The only clue was a trail of bloody clothes leading to the well house.
上帝啊 我们可以续写《未解之谜》了
Jesus. We can get Derry on Unsolved Mysteries.
- 那就写吧 你可是个天才 - 也许吧
- Let's do that. You're brilliant. - I might be.
不知道
I don't know.
也许他只是想交一些朋友 斯坦利
Maybe he's just trying to make some friends, Stanley.
那个井房在哪?
Where was the well house?
我也不知道 可能是在镇上的某个地方
I don't know. Somewhere in town, I guess.
怎么了
Why?
没什么
Nothing.
没有人能与我感同身受
Nobody knows the trouble I've seen...
没人知道我的悲伤
Nobody knows my sorrow...
埃迪…
Eddie...
你在找什么?
What are you looking for?
哦
Oh!
见鬼 我妈会杀了我的
Fuck. My mom's gonna fucking flip.
你觉得这药对我有用吗 埃迪?
Do you think this will help me, Eddie?
救命啊
Help! Help!
埃迪 你要去哪?
Where you going, Eds?
如果你住在这 那你已经到家了
If you lived here, you'd be home by now.
来一起做小丑吧 埃迪
Come join the clown, Eds.
你会在这里漂浮起来
You'll float down here.
我们都在这儿漂浮着
We all float down here.
我们漂浮着
Yes, we do.
君之红发婉如冬日烈火
"Your hair is winter fire...
而燃至柳月的余烬
"January embers...
亦为我心焚炼之地
"My heart burns there, too. "
贝弗利…
Beverly...
Beverly.
救救我
Help me.
请救救我
Help me, please.
我们都很想见你 贝弗利
We all want to meet you, Beverly.
我们都在下面漂浮着呢
We all float down here.
谁在说话? 是谁?
Hello? Who are you?
- 我是维罗妮卡 - 贝蒂·瑞普森
- I'm Veronica. - Betty Ripsom.
帕特里克·霍克斯德特
Patrick Hockstetter.
再靠近些
Come closer.
- 你想看看吗? - 我们在漂浮
- Wanna see? - We float.
我们变了
We change.
爸爸
Daddy!
救命
Help!
救命啊
这儿他妈的发生了什么?
The hell's going on?
水池…
The sink...
那里有血 在那…
And the blood... It's...
什么血
What blood?
水池里 你没看见吗?
The sink. You don't see it?
那里面有血
There was blood.
你让我很操心 贝弗
You worry me, Bevvie.
你真的让我很操心
You worry me a lot.
你看不到吗?
But don't you see?
你为什么要剪短头发?
Why'd you do this to your hair?
看着像是个男孩
Makes you look like a boy.
乔治
Georgie.
我把船弄丢了 比尔 不要生气
I lost it, Billy. Don't be mad.
我没有生你的气
I'm not mad at you.
我只是在漂浮
It just floated off.
但是 比尔 如果你跟我一起走的话
But, Bill, if you'll come with me,
你也会漂浮起来
you'll float, too.
乔治
Georgie.
你也会漂浮起来…
You'll float, too. You'll float, too.
你也会漂浮起来
You'll float, too.
- 你也会漂浮起来 - 你也会漂浮起来
- You'll float, too. - You'll float, too.
你也会漂浮起来…
You'll float, too. You'll float, too.
你也会漂浮起来
You'll float, too.
你也会漂浮起来…
You'll float, too! You'll float, too!
你也会漂浮起来
You'll float, too!
不 我们必须穿过巷子
No, we gotta go through the alleyway.
巷子太长了
The alley takes way too long.
不 巷子快得多
No, the alley is so much faster.
巷子更危险 更讨厌
The alley is more dangerous and it's disgusting.
怎么可能会危险?
How is it more dangerous?
因为这闻起来像狗屎 还很恶心
It smells like piss and it's gross.
- 我就是不喜欢 怎样? - 我的天啊
- Just take the side streets for once. - Oh, my God.
所以你就决定不喜欢这样的事情 你个混蛋
The side streets are the same. They smell like piss and shit.
好吧 她要说的那件事实际上是什么?
Okay, okay. Can you just tell me what she said exactly?
她什么也没说
She didn't say anything.
他就是说你们得快点过来
She just said that you guys need to hurry over.
她什么也没说 好 好吧
She didn't say anything. Okay. Okay.
我们到了 我
You made it. I...
我需要给你们看些东西
I need to show you something.
看什么?
What is it?
比在采石场露的还多?
More than we saw at the quarry?
闭嘴吧你 里奇
Shut up! Just shut up, Richie.
如果我爸发现我带男孩子进家 他会杀了我的
My dad will kill me if he finds out I had boys in the apartment.
我 我 我们会留下人望风
Then we'll leave a lookout.
里奇 你留在这
Richie, stay here.
喂喂喂 要是她爸爸回来了怎么办?
Whoa, whoa, whoa! What if her dad comes back?
向他展现你嘴炮本色
Do what you always do. Start talking.
这可是一种天赋
It is a gift.
在里面
In there.
那里面有什么?
What is it?
你会看到的
You'll see.
很好 把我们带去洗手间
Are you taking us to your bathroom?
你难道不知道89%的意外事故
I just want you to know that 89% of the worst accidents in homes...
都是在厨房或者洗手间发生的?
are caused in bathrooms.
那里面滋生超级多的细菌和真菌…
And, I mean, that's where all the bacteria and fungi are...
可不是个卫生的地方…
and it's not a really sanitary place...
我就知道
I knew it!
你们有看到吗?
You see it?
- 是的 - 这
- Yes. - What...
这里发生了什么?
What happened in here?
我爸爸看不到这些 我当时觉得可能是我疯了
My dad couldn't see it. I thought I might be crazy.
如果是你疯了 那么我们也都疯了
Well, if you're crazy, then we're all crazy.
我们得帮她把这里清理干净
We can't leave it like this.
你从来没去过德里镇的夏日集市吗?
All right, so you've never been to the Derry Summer Fair?
不 我没去过
No, I don't think so.
我记着应该是没去过
Not that I know of.
我每年都去
Well, I go there every year,
有一次我和里奇去的 我击中了靶心获得头奖
but I was there one time with Richie and technically won 'cause I hit the target.
但是奖品太多了 我都不知道该选 选哪个
But there were so many prizes, I didn't know which to pick.
他们污蔑我的那些话
It's not true, you know.
那都不是真的
What they say about me.
我只被一个男人吻过
I was only ever kissed by one guy.
那是在很久很久之前的事情了
It was a long time ago.
不过那一吻我一直记得
It was a nice kiss though.
燃至柳月的余烬
"January embers. "
是当时那舞台剧中的台词吗?
Was that in the play?
不 是一首诗
No, the poem.
哦
Oh...
我读过的诗 诗并不多
Oh, I don't really know much poetry.
哦 我只是
Oh. I was just...
当我没说
Never mind then.
哦
Um...
我只是想让你知道
Just so you know, I...
我从来不相信那些谣言
I never believed any of the rumors.
我们这群人都不相信
And none of us Losers do.
我们喜欢和你一起玩
We like hanging with you.
谢谢
Thanks.
你不用总是对我们说谢谢
You shouldn't thank us too much.
总和我们玩 你会被划成我们同一类人的
Hanging out with us makes you a Loser, too.
没事的
I can take that.
不 我是真太乐意做你们的私人门卫
No, I love being your personal doorman, really.
你们这帮蠢货还能再磨蹭一点吗?
Could you idiots have taken any longer?
- 闭嘴吧 里奇 - 是的 快闭嘴吧 里奇
- All right, shut up, Richie. - Yeah, shut up, Richie.
好吧好吧 不让我喷垃圾话 我懂了
Oh, okay, trash the trashmouth, I get it.
嘿 我可不是某个擦浴室地板的倒霉蛋
Hey, I wasn't the one scrubbing the bathroom floor...
想象她的水槽像是万圣节时艾迪妈妈的阴道
and imagining that her sink went all Eddie's mom's vagina on Halloween.
她没有瞎想
She didn't imagine it.
我
I...
我也看见了一些诡异的东西
I saw something, too.
你也看见血了?
You saw blood, too?
不是血
Not blood.
我看见了乔 乔 乔治
I saw Georgie.
感觉很真实
It seemed so real.
我是说 它看着很像乔治 但是那其实是…
I mean, it seemed like him, but there was this...
是一个小丑
The clown.
是的 我也看见他了
Yeah, I saw him, too.
等等 是不是只有处子之身才能看到这些东西?
Wait, can only virgins see this stuff?
所以我才看不见那个玩意儿?
Is that why I'm not seeing this shit?
该死 那是贝尔奇·哈金斯的车
Oh, shit, that's Belch Huggins' car.
- 我们该走了 - 同意
- We should probably get outta here. - Yeah.
你们看 那个自行车是家里蹲男孩儿的吧?
Wait, isn't that the homeschooled kid's bike?
是的 是麦克的
Yeah, that's Mike's.
我们必须帮他
We have to help him.
一定要去吗?
We should?
当然
Yes.
来吧
Come on.
吃了它
Eat that meat!
- 吃了它 - 蠢蛋
- Eat it, bitch! - You little fucker!
- 混蛋 - 傻逼
- Bitch! - Motherfucker!
- 吃了它啊 小婊子 - 混蛋
- Eat it, you little bitch! - Pussy!
该死…
Fucking...
你要做什么?
Whatcha gonna do, huh?
站起来
Get up!
快给我站起来
Get the fuck up!
真是个蠢货
You little fucker!
快 亨利 用力砸
Come on, Henry, smack him!
你这个小婊子
You little bitch.
- 扔得好 - 谢谢
- Nice throw. - Thanks.
你们这帮废物想上她不用这么费劲
You losers are trying too hard.
只要你们软语相求
She'll do you.
她会跟你们啪啪啪的
You just gotta ask nicely,
我以前就是这么做的
like I did.
你他妈敢动手?
What the fuck?
快 砸他
Come on, get 'em! Fuck!
石头之战
Rock war!
- 用力砸 - 小心
- Get 'em! - Watch out!
砸死你们这帮混蛋
Fuck you, motherfuckers!
埃迪
Eddie!
- 滚开 - 呃
- Fuck outta here! - Ow!
该死
Ah, shit!
去死 贱人
Fuck you, bitch!
快扔 砸死他们
Come on, guys! Let's get 'em!
- 他妈的 - 快他妈离开这里
- Fuck this. - Fuck out of here.
他妈的 废材
Fuck you, losers!
去给你爸爸吹箫吧 你这个乡村非主流
Go blow your dad, you mullet-wearing asshole!
谢谢你们 但是你们不该惹那伙人的
Thanks, guys, but you shouldn't have done that.
他们也会对付你们的
They'll be after you guys, too, now.
鲍尔斯 他一直都想对付我们
Oh, no, no, no. Bowers? He's always after us.
这是我们的共 共 共同点
I guess that's one thing we all have in common.
是啊 家里蹲骚年 欢迎加入废柴俱乐部
Yeah, Homeschool. Welcome to the Losers' Club.
在这里
Right there.
他们说 他们在水管旁边
They say they found part of his hand...
找到了他被啃剩下的手
all chewed up near the Standpipe.
他曾向我借过铅笔
He asked to borrow a pencil once.
她似乎已被遗 遗 遗忘了
It's like she's been forgotten...
因为现在人们关注的是科科伦失踪案
because Corcoran's missing.
这事能有完吗?
Is it ever gonna end?
兄弟 你干什么?
What the fuck, dude?
你们在讲什么?
What are you guys talking about?
还不是之前他们讲的那件事情
What they always talk about.
其实我觉得这事会结束
I actually think it will end.
至少会消停一段时间
For a little while, at least.
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
我仔细检查了我搜集到的德里镇资料
So I was going over all my Derry research...
标注出了所有的大事件
and I charted out all the big events.
1908年钢铁厂爆炸事件
The Ironworks explosion in 1908,
1935年布拉德利团伙覆灭事件
the Bradley Gang in '35,
1962年黑斑点俱乐部焚毁事件
and The Black Spot in '62.
还有现在孩子失踪…
And now kids being...
我发现这些大事件似乎是
I realized this stuff seems to happen...
每隔27年发生一次
Every 27 years.
好吧 那我来梳理一下整件事
Okay, so, let me get this straight.
在一年之中 小丑会到处吃孩子
It comes out from wherever to eat kids for, like, a year?
然后呢? 再休眠27年?
And then what? It just goes into hibernation?
也许这就像… 那个东西叫什么来着?
Maybe it's like... What do you call it?
蝉
Cicadas.
蝉每隔十七年出来一次
You know, the bugs that come out once every 17 years.
我爷爷认为这个镇子被诅咒了
My grandfather thinks this town is cursed.
他说
He says that...
就因为某种东西的存在
all the bad things that happen in this town...
所有的坏事情都在这个小镇发生
are because of one thing.
一个以德里镇人为食的邪恶的东西
An evil thing that feeds off the people of Derry.
但我觉着不可能只是一种怪物
But it can't be one thing.
我们看到的怪物都不一样
We all saw something different.
也许吧
Maybe.
或者它让我们看到我们最害怕的东西
Or maybe It knows what scares us most and that's what we see.
我 我看到了一个麻风病人
I saw a leper.
他就像是一个行走的感染源
He was like a walking infection.
但其实你根本没遇到这个人
But you didn't.
因为那怪物不是真实的
Because it isn't real.
全都是幻觉
None of this is.
埃迪看到的麻风病人是幻觉
Not Eddie's leper...
比尔看到的乔治也是
or Bill seeing Georgie...
我总能看到的那个女人也是幻觉
or the woman I keep seeing.
她性感吗?
She hot?
不 里奇
No, Richie.
她不性感
She's not hot.
她的脸很恐怖
Her face is all messed up.
这些事没一样能讲得通
None of this makes any sense.
它们都像噩梦一样
They're all like bad dreams.
我觉得不对 我知道现实与噩梦的区别 好吗?
I don't think so. I know the difference between a bad dream and real life, okay?
你看到了什么? 你也看到了不好的东西吗?
What'd you see? You saw something, too?
是的
Yes.
你们知道哈里斯大街上烧毁的那栋房子吗?
Do you guys know that burned-down house on Harris Avenue?
大火烧楼的时候 我被困在里面
I was inside when it burned down.
在我获救之前…
Before I was rescued,
我爸妈都被困在隔壁的房间
my mom and dad were trapped in the next room over from me.
他们大力地推门 砸门
They were pushing and pounding on the door,
试图找到我
trying to get to me.
快点 儿子
Hurry, son!
我快被烧死了
It burns!
但是火势太大了
But it was too hot.
等消防员们找到他们
When the firemen finally found them,
他们的手已被烧得可以看到骨头
the skin on their hands had melted down to the bone.
我们都有惧怕的东西
We're all afraid of something.
这话说得对
Got that right.
怎么了里奇 你害怕什么?
Why, Rich? What are you afraid of?
小丑
Clowns.
好了
Okay.
快看
Look.
乔治就是在那里失踪的
That's where Georgie disappeared.
钢铁厂
There's the Ironworks.
黑斑点夜总会
And The Black Spot.
所有坏事发生的地方 都有下水道连接
Everywhere it happens, it's all connected by the sewers.
而那些下水管道
And they all meet up at the...
汇集点就是井房
The well house.
是内波特街上的那栋房子
It's in the house on Neibolt Street.
你是说瘾君子和流浪汉那类货色们聚集的那个鬼屋?
You mean that creepy-ass house where all the junkies and hobos like to sleep?
我可不喜欢那个地方
I hate that place.
我总觉得里面有什么东西在看我
It always feels like it's watching me.
我就是在那里看到它的
That's where I saw It.
我在那看见一个小丑
That's where I saw the clown.
那 那 那就是它的老巢
That's where It lives.
我想象出有什么东西会想住在那种地方
I can't imagine anything ever wanting to live there.
我们可不可以不要谈这个话题了?
Can we stop talking about this?
我快不能呼吸了
I can barely breathe.
这是暑假
This is summer.
我们是小孩 我快不能呼吸了
We're kids. I can barely breathe.
我他妈哮喘病都要发作了
I'm up here having a fucking asthma attack.
我可不想再看这个破玩意
I'm not doing this.
搞什么 把地图贴回去
What the hell? Put the map back.
嗯 嗯
Mmm-mmm.
怎么了?
What happened?
这是怎么了?
What's going on?
我不知道 快看
I got it. Hold on.
伙计们
Guys.
乔治
Georgie.
比尔
Bill?
什么鬼
What the fuck?
是它
It's It!
那他妈的是什么?
What the fuck is that? What the fuck is that?
我他妈也不知道啊
I don't fucking know!
关了它
Turn it off! Turn it off!
快关了它
Yeah. Yeah, turn it off. Turn it off!
斯坦利 快跑
Run, Stanley!
那是什么鬼?
What is it?
怎么搞的?
What the fuck?
本 谢谢你
Thanks, Ben.
它看见我们了
It saw us.
它能看见我们 它知道我们在这
It saw us, and it knows where we are.
它一直知道
It always did.
好吧 我们出发吧
So, let's go.
出发?
Go?
去哪?
Go where?
内波特街
Neibolt.
乔 乔 乔治就在那里
That's where Georgie is.
我们刚逃过一劫 还去?
After that?
是的 现在是暑假 我们都应该呆在外面…
Yeah, it's summer. We should be outside.
你他妈的别再跟我提现在是暑 暑 暑假
If you say it's summer one more fucking time...
比尔?
Bill!
等等
Wait!
只见他猛 猛挥拳头
"He thrusts his fists...
往柱 柱 柱子上砸
"against the posts...
直说自己把鬼 鬼 鬼碰
"and still insists he sees..."
比尔
Bill!
比尔 你不能进去
Bill, you can't go in there.
这太疯狂了
This is crazy.
听着 你们不用非得跟我一起进去
Look, you don't have to come in with me.
但是当另一个乔治
But what happens when another Georgie goes missing?
或是另一个贝蒂 另一个科科伦 又或是
Or another Betty? Or another Ed Corcoran? Or...
我们几个其中之一失踪
one of us?
你们打算像镇子里的其他人一样
Are you just gonna pretend it isn't happening...
假装什么事情都没发生吗?
like everyone else in this town?
我不能
Because I can't.
我回到家就不由自主地想到失踪的乔治
I go home, and all I see is that Georgie isn't there.
他的衣服 他的玩具 那些傻傻的动物毛绒玩偶都在家
His clothes, his toys, his stupid stuffed animals, but...
但是他不在了
He isn't.
所以对于我来说
So walking into this house,
走进这间房子
for me,
比走进我自己家更容易
it's easier than walking into my own.
哇哦
Wow.
怎么了
What?
他刚才一点也没结巴
He didn't stutter once.
等等
Wait!
嗯
Um...
呃 我们不需要望风的人吗
Shouldn't we have some people keep watch?
就是…为了以防万一
You know, just in case something bad happens?
谁 谁 谁想留在外面
Who wants to stay out here?
该死
Fuck.
我真不敢相信我抽到了下下签
I can't believe I pulled the short straw.
要是按丁丁的长度来的话 倒霉的就是你们了
You guys are lucky you're not measuring dicks.
闭嘴 里奇
Shut up, Richie.
我闻到它了
I can smell it.
不要用嘴呼吸
Don't breathe through your mouth.
为什么?
How come?
因为你在吃它的残渣
Because then you're eating it.
这是什么?
What?
这上面说我失踪了
It... It says I'm missing.
你 你 你没有失踪 里奇
You're not missing, Richie.
德里市警察局
"Police department, City of Derry. "
这是我的衬衫 我的发型 是我的脸
That's my shirt. That's my hair. That's my face.
冷静 这都是假的
Calm down, this isn't real.
有我的名字 我的年龄 还有日期…
That's my name. That's my age! That's the date!
这不是真的 里奇
It can't be real, Richie.
这他妈的是什么? 上面写着我失踪了
No, it says it! What the fuck?
- 我失踪了吗? - 冷静一下
- Am I missing? Am I gonna go missing? - Calm down. Calm down.
看着我 里奇 看着我
Look at me, Richie. Look at me.
这不是真实的
That... That isn't real.
它在戏弄我们
It's playing tricks on you.
嗨?
Hello?
有人吗?
帮帮我
Help me, please!
贝蒂?
Betty?
瑞普森?
Ripsom?
埃迪…
Eddie...
你在找什么?
What are you looking for?
伙计们 你们听到了吗?
Guys, can you hear that?
她刚刚就在这 她他妈的去哪了?
She was just here. Where the fuck did she go?
伙计们?
Guys.
哦 上帝
Oh, my God.
伙计们?
Guys. Guys!
- 伙计们 - 埃迪
- Guys! Guys! - What? Eddie?
该死
What the fuck?
该吃药了 埃迪
Time to take your pill, Eddie.
- 埃迪 打开门 - 里奇
- Eddie. Open the door! - Richie.
你还好吗?
You okay?
埃迪 发生什么了?
Eddie, what's going on?
埃迪
Eds.
Eddie.
嘿 里奇
Come here, Richie.
埃迪
Eddie.
你他妈的在哪
Where the fuck are you?
我们不是在捉迷藏 蠢货
We're not playing hide-and-seek, dipshit.
里奇?
Richie?
里奇 里奇
Richie! Richie!
比尔 开门 快开门
Bill, come on, open the door.
打不开啊
It won't open!
- 这到底是怎么回事? 里奇 - 我打不开
- What's going on? Richie! - I can't!
打开门 里奇
Open the door, Rich.
哦 糟了
Oh, shit.
该死的小丑
Stupid clowns.
见鬼
Oh, fuck.
啊
Ugh!
发现你喽 里奇
Beep-beep, Richie.
我们快离开这
Let's get outta here.
来玩看谁吐的远吧?
You wanna play loogie?
来漂浮吧
Time to float.
我的鞋呢?
Where's my shoe?
我操 她的腿呢?
Where the fuck were her legs?
这又是什么鬼?
Holy shit, what the fuck was that?
这不是真的
This isn't real.
记得那个失踪孩子的海报吗?
Remember the missing kid poster.
那个不是真的 所以这个也不是真的
That wasn't real, so this isn't real.
美味可口的恐惧
Tasty, tasty, beautiful fear.
来吧 准备好了吗?
Come on. Ready?
没有
No!
不要
No.
不 不要
No, no!
谢天谢地
Oh, thank fuck.
- 埃迪呢? - 救命
- Where's Eddie? - Help!
救命
Help!
埃迪
Eddie!
见鬼
Holy fuck.
埃迪?
Eddie!
比尔 这下你信了吗?
This isn't real enough for you, Billy?
你还不信我是真的吗?
I'm not real enough for you?
我靠
Oh, shit.
乔治觉得我是真的哦
It was real enough for Georgie.
哦 天哪
Holy shit!
- 去救埃迪 - 去救埃迪
- Get Eddie! - Get Eddie!
天啊 我们快离开这
Oh, fuck! We gotta get out of here!
带上埃迪 快走
Get Eddie. Let's go!
伙计们 小心
Guys, watch out!
- 不 不 不 不要 - 艾迪 看着我
- No, no, no, no! - Eddie, look at me!
伙计们
He's gonna get us! Guys!
不
No!
本
Ben!
我们快离开这儿
Let's get out of here!
别让小丑跑了
Don't let him get away!
比尔 我们得先救埃迪
Bill, we have to help Eddie!
不 不
No! No!
我来把手臂掰回去
I'm gonna snap your arm into place.
你别想碰我
Rich, do not fucking touch me.
- 那么开始了 一 二 三 - 我说了别他妈碰我
- Okay, one, two, three. - Do not touch me!
靠
Holy shit!
是你们把他弄伤的
You. You did this.
他身体很弱的你们知道的
You know how delicate he is.
- 我们被攻击了 卡斯布拉克夫人 - 不 不
- We were attacked, Mrs. K. - No. Don't.
别说了 别想着怪别人
Don't try and blame anyone else.
- 我来吧 - 不用
- Let me help. - Get back!
我可是听过你的那些事的 马什小姐
Oh, I've heard of you, Miss Marsh.
你个脏女人别碰我的孩子
And I don't want a dirty girl like you touching my son.
卡斯布拉克夫人 我…
Mrs. K, I...
别说了 都是小畜生 全都是
No! You are all monsters. All of you.
埃迪不会再和你们玩了 听见了吗 再也不会了
And Eddie is done with you. Do you hear? Done!
我看见那口井了
I saw the well.
我 我 们已知那口井的位置了
We know where it is...
下次我们会准备得更充分
and next time we'll be better prepared.
不
No!
没有下次了 比尔
No next time, Bill.
- 你疯了 - 怎么这么说?
- You're insane. - Why?
我们都清楚没人会来帮我们消灭它
We all know no one else is going to do anything.
埃迪刚才差点没命了 你再看看这倒霉孩子
Eddie was nearly killed! And look at this motherfucker.
他流了那么多血
He's leaking Hamburger Helper!
可是我们不能就让他这样逃了
We can't pretend it's gonna go away.
本 你自己也说了 它每27年回来一次
Ben, you said it yourself, It comes back every 27 years.
好 那时候我都40岁了 早就不在这里了
Fine! I'll be 40 and far away from here.
你说过你也想离开这里的
I thought you said you wanted to get out of this town, too.
我说离开是想奔向更好的生活 不是逃离这里
Because I wanna run towards something. Not away.
抱歉打断一下 是谁让莫林·林沃德成为我们一员的?
I'm sorry, who invited Molly Ringwald into the group?
- 里奇… - 我们还是现实点吧
- Richie... - I'm just saying, let's face facts.
看看现实世界
Real world.
乔治已经死了 别想把我们的命也搭进去
Georgie is dead. Stop trying to get us killed, too.
乔治没有死
Georgie's not dead.
当初你没能救他 但现在你至少可以救你自己
You couldn't save him, but you can still save yourself.
不 收 收回你刚才的话
No, take it back.
你害怕 我们也都很怕 但是收回刚才的话
You're scared and we all are, but take it back!
比尔
Bill!
你个废物
You're just a bunch of losers!
- 放开我 - 里奇 别说了
- Fuck off! - Richie, stop.
你俩都是废物 你们俩都会送命的
You're just a bunch of losers and you'll get yourselves killed...
- 就为了抓一个傻小丑 - 别吵了
- trying to catch a fucking stupid clown. - Stop!
"它"就是想看我们这样
This is what It wants.
"它"想让我们内讧
It wants to divide us.
我们听见他出现时 是因为我们团结
We were all together when we hurt It.
所以我们才能活下来
That's why we're still alive.
是 但我想继续活下去
Yeah? Well, I plan to keep it that way.
- 麦克… - 伙计们…
- Mike... - Guys...
我做不到
I can't do this.
我爷爷是对的
My granddad was right.
我只是个旁观者 插不了手
I'm an outsider. Gotta stay that way.
- 耶 得分 - 真准
- Yeah! Bonus! - Yeah, there we go.
换下一个靶子
Put the next target out there.
抓好了
Just hold it.
你们在干吗?
What the hell's going on here?
按你的要求 帮你擦枪
Just cleaning your gun, like you asked.
帮我擦枪?
You're cleaning my gun, huh?
- 爸爸… - 嘿
- Dad... - Hey!
现在你们几个再看看他
Look at him now, boys.
只会玩点假把式算什么东西
Ain't nothing like a little fear to make a paper man crumble.
来取药吗 埃迪?
Here for the refills, Eddie?
是
Yeah.
这些都没用 你知道的吧?
You know it's all bullshit, right?
什么没用?
What is?
你的药
Your medication.
都是安慰剂而已
They're placebos.
安慰剂是什么意思?
What's placebo mean?
安慰剂就是扯淡的意思
Placebo means bullshit.
你没有朋友吧?
No friends, huh?
你的石膏
Your cast.
上面没有签名之类的吗?
No signatures or anything?
真可怜
So sad.
我不想把它弄脏
I didn't want it to get dirty.
我给你签一个吧
I'll sign it for you.
亨利 你还好吧?
You okay, Henry?
我最喜欢的午后节目环节就是
And this is my most favorite part of the afternoon.
听你们的故事
Getting to know all about so many of you.
有谁想分享自己的故事吗?
Is there someone here that wants to share with us...
- 大家今天最开心的事是什么? - 我
- what they most enjoyed about today? - Me!
你呢?
How about you?
我今天见到小丑了 很开心
I liked seeing the clown.
真的吗? 你们想见小丑?
You did? You liked the clown?
是的
Yes!
切尔茜呢 你喜欢什么?
What about the rest of you?
我喜欢漂浮的泡泡
I liked when the bubbles float.
是吗? 我也喜欢
You did? Me too.
我喜欢看东西飘起来
I just love watching things float.
我们都飘起来吧
We all float.
说得好
That's right.
你也是哦 亨利
And you will, too, Henry.
享受美好的一天吧
Make it a wonderful day.
杀了他
Kill him.
杀了他 杀了他
Kill him. Kill him.
干得漂亮 大家给他热烈鼓掌
Oh, no. Give a big round of applause!
干得好 亨利
Well done, Henry.
把他们杀光 把他们都杀光
Kill them all. Kill them all.
把他们都杀光
Kill them all!
把他们杀光 把他们杀光 把他们都杀光
Kill them all! Kill them all! Kill them all!
你偷偷摸摸地要去哪?
Where are you sneaking off to?
不去哪 爸爸
Nowhere, Daddy.
你特意打扮过了
You're looking prettied up.
我没有特意打扮 爸爸 我每天都是这样穿的
I'm not prettied up, Daddy. I wear this almost every day.
过来
Come.
我很担心你 小贝弗
You know I worry about you, Bevvie.
我知道
I know.
有人和我说了些关于你的事
People in town have been saying some things to me about you.
说你整个暑假都和一帮男孩混在一起
Sneaking around all summer long with a bunch of boys.
一群人里就你一个女孩
The only girl in the pack.
他们只是朋友 我发誓
They're just friends, I swear.
我知道男孩子是怎么看你的 小贝弗
I know what's in boys' minds when they look at you, Bevvie.
我太懂了
I know all too well.
我的手…
My hand...
你和那些男孩在树林里做那种事吗?
Are you doing womanly things down in the woods with those boys?
没 没有 你不用担心 我保证
No, no, no, nothing. You don't have to worry. I promise.
这是什么?
What's this?
没什么 只是一首诗
It's nothing. It's just a poem.
只是一首诗?
Just a poem?
那你怎么把它藏在你内衣抽屉里?
But you had to hide it in your underwear drawer.
你为什么要藏在那种地方?
Why would you have to hide it there?
你还是我的小宝贝吗?
Are you still my girl?
不是
No.
你说什么?
What did you say?
我说我不是
I said, no!
不
No!
走开 不要
Get away, no!
不 放手
Get off!
不
No!
那些男孩 他们知不知道你是我的…
Those boys. Do they know that you're my...
贝弗利?
Beverly?
贝弗利
Beverly!
- 里奇 - 你想怎么着?
- Richie. - What do you want?
你看这个我在揍的人 我当他是你
See that guy I'm hitting? I'm pretending it's you.
它捉走了贝弗利
It got Beverly.
你在说啥?
What are you talking about?
是"它" 里奇
It, Richie.
贝弗利被"它"捉住了
It got Beverly.
喂?
Hello?
好的
Okay.
我会去的
I'll meet you there.
你这是要去哪?
And just where do you think you're off to?
去见朋友
Out with my friends.
宝贝 你不能去
Sweetie, you can't go.
你病还没好 知道吗?
You're getting over your sickness, remember?
我的病?
My sickness?
好吧 我生什么病了 妈妈?
Okay, what sickness, Ma?
你知道这些是什么药吗? 是安慰剂
You know what these are? They're gazebos!
都是骗人的
They're bullshit!
这药对你有好处 埃迪
They help you, Eddie.
我这是在保护你
I had to protect you.
保护我?
Protect me?
对我说谎还把我关在这个地狱里?
By lying to me? By keeping me locked inside this hellhole?
我不想这么说
I'm sorry but the only people that were...
但是只有我的朋友真的想保护我
actually trying to protect me were my friends.
在我真正需要他们的时候 你却让我背叛了他们
And you made me turn my back on them when I really needed them.
所以我现在要去
So I'm going.
埃迪 不行
Eddie. Eddie. No.
你马上给我回来
You get back here.
- 我要见我的朋友 - 埃迪
- Sorry, Mom, I gotta go save my friends. - Eddie!
别这样对我 埃迪
Don't do this to me, Eddie!
伙计们 上尖刺
Guys, spikes.
斯坦利?
Stan?
斯坦利 我们一定要去
Stan, we all have to go.
贝弗利说得对
Beverly was right.
要是我们像上次那样分开 小丑会把我们各个击破
If we split up like last time, that clown will kill us one by one.
但只要我们团结在一起
But if we stick together,
我们一起…
all of us,
我们就能赢
we'll win.
我保证
I promise.
埃迪 你有硬币吗?
Hey, Eddie, you got a quarter?
我才不要在这鬼玩意里许愿
I wouldn't want to make a wish in that fucking thing.
贝弗利
Beverly?
我们要怎么下去?
How are we supposed to get down there?
行了 来吧
All right. Come on.
好了 兄弟
All right.
伙计们 帮帮我
Guys, guys. Help.
- 你没事吧 伙计 - 是 我没事
- All right, buddy? - Yeah, I'm okay.
上来 贝弗利 上来吧
Step right up, Beverly. Step right up.
来换装 来漂浮 你会笑 你会哭
Come change. Come float. You'll laugh. You'll cry.
你会欢呼 你会死
You'll cheer. You'll die.
为大家介绍 会跳舞者小丑:潘尼怀斯
Introducing Pennywise the Dancing Clown.
我不怕你
I'm not afraid of you.
我会让你怕的
You will be.
救命
Help! Help me!
啊
Ahhh!
去死吧
Die!
麦克
Mike!
- 麦克 - 麦克
- Mike! - Mike!
你没事吧 麦克?
You okay? Mike!
鲍尔斯
Bowers.
麦克 靠
Mike. Fuck.
- 麦克 - 他在哪?
- Mike! - Where is he?
他要对我们下手了
We're next.
不
No, no, no!
- 抓住 - 抓住绳子
- Grab it! - Get the rope! Get the rope!
哦 该死
Oh, shit.
- 麦克 - 麦克
- Mike! - Mike!
别碰他
Leave him alone!
你不听我的话是不是?
You didn't listen to what I told you, did you?
你该离开德里镇的
You should've stayed out of Derry.
你父母没走 结果呢
Your parents didn't and look what happened to them.
每次路过那些骨灰 我都好伤心
I still get sad every time I pass by that pile of ashes.
好伤心
Sad,
如果是我放的火就好了
that I couldn't have done it myself.
快跑 麦克
Run, Mike!
麦克
Mike!
别想起来
Fuck down!
我要 要 要上去
I should get up there.
你疯了吗? 你怎么上得去?
Are you insane? With what?
天啊
Holy shit.
- 天啊… - 麦克
- Oh, my... - Mike!
我没事
I'm okay.
该死
Shoot!
斯坦利
Stanley.
贝弗利?
Beverly?
是你吗?
Is that you?
伙计们?
Guys?
是你们吗?
- 什么 - 快 伙计们 斯坦利呢?
- What? - Guys, where's Stan?
斯坦利
Stanley!
Stan!
哦 天啊 又是灰水
Oh, shit. Greywater.
斯坦利?
Stan?
斯坦利
Stanley!
- 斯坦利 - 噢 斯坦利
- Stan! - Shit! Stan!
斯坦利
Stanley!
- 我们马上来了 坚持住 - 别害怕 我们马上就来了
- We're coming, man! - We're coming! Don't worry.
- 斯坦利? - 斯坦利 斯坦利
- Stan? - Stanley! Stan!
他的手电
His flashlight!
那他妈是什么鬼?
What the fuck is that thing?
天啊
Oh, shit.
靠
该死
Oh, shit!
天啊
斯坦利
Stanley!
- 斯坦利 斯坦利 - 斯坦利
- Stanley! Stan! - Stanley!
不 不 别过来
No! No! No!
没事了
It's okay.
你们不要我了 你们把我带到内波特街
You left me! You took me into Neibolt!
你们不是我的朋友
You're not my friends!
是你们逼我来内波特街
You made me go into Neibolt!
斯坦利 对不起
Stanley, I'm sorry.
是你们逼我来内波特街
You made me go into Neibolt!
都是你的错
This is your fault.
我们不会让你出事的
We would never let anything happen to you.
我们就在这儿
We're here for you.
我们不会那样对你的 我们走
You know we wouldn't do that to you. Come on.
比尔 比尔
Bill! Bill!
比尔
Bill!
贝弗利
Beverly!
我会回来救你的 贝弗利
I'll come back for you, Bev.
比尔?
Bill!
比尔
快点
Come on.
咱们离开这吧 这是灰水
Get out of there, dude. That's greywater.
等等 天啊 我的手电呢?
Wait, wait, wait. Oh, my God, my fucking flashlight?
埃迪
Eddie!
快 我们快离开这儿 快点
Come on, let's get the fuck out of here! Come on!
- 天哪 - 贝弗利? 贝弗利?
- Holy shit. - Bev? Bev?
- 贝弗利? - 天啊
- Beverly? - Holy shit.
贝弗利
Bev.
她怎么会飘在半空的?
How is she in the air?
伙计们
Guys.
那些…
Are those...
失踪的孩子
The missing kids.
都在漂浮着
Floating.
- 我来抓住她 - 该死
- Just let me grab her. - Shit.
我快滑下去了
I'm slipping.
贝弗利
Bev.
Beverly.
她怎么不醒过来?
Why isn't she waking up?
她这是怎么了?
What is wrong with her?
贝弗利 拜托了 醒醒
Beverly, please! Come on!
喔 喔 喔…
Wow.
贝弗利?
Bev?
"燃至柳月的余烬"
"January embers"
"亦为我心焚炼之地"
"My heart burns there too"
我靠…
Jesus, fuck.
哦 天啊
Oh, God.
比尔呢?
Where's Bill?
乔治
Georgie.
你怎么才来?
What took you so long?
我一直在找你
I was looking for you this whole time.
我找不到出去的路
I couldn't find my way outta here.
他说我可以要回我的船 比尔
He said I could have my boat back, Billy.
她快吗?
Was she fast?
快得我跟不上它
I couldn't keep up with it.
是"她" 乔治
"She," Georgie.
船都得用"她"来称呼的
You call boats "she".
带我回家吧 比尔
Take me home, Billy.
我想回家
I wanna go home.
我好想你 我想和爸爸妈妈在一起
I miss you. I wanna be with Mom and Dad.
我最大的心愿就是你能回家
I want more than anything for you to be home.
和爸爸妈妈团聚
With Mom and Dad.
我也好想你
I miss you so much.
我爱你 比尔
I love you, Billy.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
但你不是乔治
But you're not Georgie.
杀了他 比尔 杀了他
Kill It, Bill! Kill It!
该死
Shit.
杀了他 比尔
Kill It, Bill!
杀了他 比尔 杀了他
Kill It! Bill, Kill It!
杀了他
Kill It!
- 杀了他 - 杀了他
- Kill It! - Kill!
杀了小丑
Kill It!
没装子弹
It's not loaded.
快啊 比尔 杀了他
Do it now, Bill! Kill It! Kill It!
嘿 枪没上膛
Hey! It's not loaded!
卧槽
Holy fuck.
靠
Oh, shit.
比尔 小心
Bill, watch out!
放开他
Leave him alone!
贝弗利 不
Beverly, no!
麦克
Mike!
快去帮他
Help him!
靠
Fuck!
本
Ben!
斯坦利
Stanley!
比尔
Bill!
不 不要
No, don't.
放开他
Let him go.
不
No.
我要定他了
I'll take him.
我要你们所有人
I'll take all of you.
我要吃你们的肉 尝你们的恐惧
And I'll feast on your flesh as I feed on your fear.
或者
Or,
你们走
you'll just leave us be.
我只要他留下
I will take him, only him...
然后我就沉睡过去
and then I will have my long rest...
你们会长大
and you will all live to grow and thrive...
过上幸福的生活
and lead happy lives...
直到老死再回到地下
until old age takes you back to the weeds.
走吧…
Leave...
是我把你们卷进来的
I'm the one who dragged you all into this.
我很抱 抱 抱歉
I'm so sorry.
对 对 对不起
Sorry.
走吧
Go!
我们不能就这么走了
Guys, we can't!
对不起 比尔
I'm sorry.
我早跟你说过的 比尔
I told you, Bill.
我早他妈就跟你说过了
I fucking told you.
我不想死…
I don't want to die.
是你的错
It's your fault.
你揍我脸
You punched me in the face.
你让我趟灰水
You made me walk through shitty water.
你还把我带进这个该死的恐怖巢穴
You brought me to a fucking crackhead house.
现在呢…
And now...
我他妈还得杀了这小丑
I'm gonna have to kill this fucking clown.
欢迎加入废柴俱乐部 你个混蛋
Welcome to the Losers' Club, asshole!
- 麦克 - 麦克
- Mike! - Mike!
斯坦利 当心
Stan, watch out!
麦克
Mike!
快杀了他
Kill him!
我要杀了你
I'm gonna kill you!
嗨 贝弗利 你还是我的小宝贝吗?
Hey, Bevvie. Are you still my little...
我靠
Oh, shit!
原来你杀不了贝弗利
That's why you didn't kill Beverly.
是因 因 因为她不怕你
'Cause she wasn't afraid.
我们也不怕你
And we aren't either.
不再怕了
Not anymore.
现在害怕的人是你
Now you're the one who's afraid.
因为你会饿死
Because you're gonna starve.
只见他猛挥拳头往柱子上砸…
"He thrusts his fists against the posts...
直说自己把鬼碰
"and still insists he sees the ghosts...
只见他猛挥拳头往柱子上砸
"He thrusts his fists against the posts"
恐惧…
Fear...
我知道我暑假社会实践论文该写什么了
I know what I'm doing for my summer experience essay.
伙计们
Guys. Guys.
那些孩子都飘下来了
The kids are floating down.
我只能想起来一部分 不过…
I can only remember parts,
我以为我已经死了
I thought I was dead.
我当时就感觉自己已经死了
That's what it felt like.
我看到我们一起回到那个下水道
I saw us, all of us together back in the cistern,
不过我们都长大了…
but we were older,
就像我们父母那么大
like, our parents' ages.
我们在那做 做 做什么?
What were we all doing there?
我只记得那时候的感觉
I just remember how we felt.
只记得我们很害怕
How scared we were.
我应该永远也忘不掉
I don't think I can ever forget that.
我们立个誓吧
Swear it.
我发誓
Swear...
如果"它"没有死
if It isn't dead,
如果"它"又回来了 我们也会回来
if It ever comes back, we'll come back, too.
我要走了…
I gotta go.
我恨你们
I hate you.
再见了
I'll see you later.
再见 斯坦利
Bye, Stan.
再见了 伙伴们
Bye, guys.
再见 麦克
Bye, Mike.
再见 废柴
See you later, losers.
再见 比尔
See you around, Bill.
再见 瑞奇
See you, Rich.
再见了伙计们
See you guys later.
再见 本
Bye, Ben.
你要搬去波特兰吗?
You all packed for Portland?
嗯 是吧
Yeah, pretty much.
我明早出发
I'm going tomorrow morning.
你会去多久?
How long will you be gone?
我姨妈说我想在那住多久都行
My aunt, she says I can stay for as long as I want, so...
我想告诉你
Just so you know...
和你们在一起的时候我 一点都不觉得自己是废柴
I never felt like a loser when I was with all of you.
回头见了
See you around.
再见
Bye.